myphone.ae 2016-10-24

# privacy english

This policy was last updated on March 2, 2015 and officially effective.  

Dear visitor, we respect your privacy and it is important to us. Below is the our privacy and security policy:

### Security

Protecting customers information is one of our top priorities. 

You personal information submitted via the website is protected both online and offline.

Whenever you are asked to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with 256 bit encryption. If your browser supports SSL (most current browsers do), it will automatically encrypt the information you provide to us on the secure pages on our site, before sending it to internet or other third party.  

Access to your personal details information is restricted to only our employees who require this information to fulfil your order.

All our servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations, with access strictly monitored and protected. Internet access is protected and restricted by firewalls and password protection. 

### Cookies

When you visit our site, we will ask your browser to place a permanent "cookie" (a very small text file) on your computer. If your browser is configured to accept cookies, it will accept the cookie and place it on your computer's hard drive. We collect this information solely for marketing purposes : to analyze where our customers are coming from, how often they visit our site and other behavior. We also collect certain technical information from your computer, like your IP address and the address of a referring web site, if any. This information will allow us to enhance our site to our customer's preferences. This information is used only for the benefit of us and you, our customer.

You can still visit our site without cookies if you choose to do so. However, please be aware that if you refuse cookies some site features may malfunction or may be slower. To visit our site without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is set. Check the browsers help menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

  * Some of our business partners (retargeting and advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over this process.

### Registration

In order to place an orders on our website, you must complete the registration form. During registration, you will be asked to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and shipping address. This information is required to provide you with our services and order status updates. You can update this information at any time by clicking on the "my account" link at the top of every page and accesing your account.

### Order

Information collected in the registration process is used solely to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used to process and fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing your order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. Information exchange process is protected by SSL. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.  

### Information Collection and Usage 

myphone.ae is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers only in order to enchance your shopping experience, process orders, update order status, marketing and promotional purposes. Information collected includes your name, telephone number, e-mail addess, shipping and billing address. All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third party. If you subscribe to receive our newsletter, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these communication. 

**Links**

  * Our site contains links to manufacturers, and other related sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of such web sites. If you click on one of these links, you will be redirected to their web site and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. Therefore, you should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they collect and handle personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses for marketing purposes, to analyze customer behavior trends, etc. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

### Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, shipment deliveries, marketing assistance, e-mail or SMS delivery, customer service, data analysis. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

We may frame or mask another website so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine Newegg.com web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Testimonials

The testimonials section of the website is for the purpose of sharing positive experiences. The testimonials section is moderated to ensure accurate and positive testimonials. Published testimonials are genuine and are not edited or altered by us. We reserves the right to post or remove any testimonial at its discretion.

By posting your comment(s) or testimonial(s) ("Testimonial") on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the Testimonial in connection with our business. You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The use of the Testimonial will be at our discretion and without compensation; (2) We may use the Testimonial with or without any pseudo (pen) name; (3) Our right to use the Testimonial is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Testimonial locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; and (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Testimonial.

Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Testimonial.

### Special Offers

Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant permission to send them such information.

Option not to receive these types of communications is offered to customers. At the time of your order,  if you do not wish to receive special offers and newsletters, you you may opt out by clicking the appropriate field. All special offers are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy:

By visiting our site you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware. Customers are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted
